feedest.com 2010-06-13

# feedest

At feedest.com, we respect the privacy of the users of our website and services and are committed to protecting it. We have created this policy to demonstrate our commitment to you and to help you understand it.

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the feedest.com website and services, post a link to the feedest.com website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties.

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.

Our services give you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. We will never automatically send you information/offers you do not want. You must choose to receive them.

Visit your feedest.com Settings to edit your profile and other information. When you're signed in, feedest.com page headers will include a link to Settings. You can delete your feedest.com account through your Settings.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we will not collect age information for users under 18 years.

feedest.com reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this feedest.com, you can send an e-mail, in English, to [privacy@feedest.com](mailto:privacy@feedest.com).

Effective Date: April 15, 2007
